http://www.jands.com.au/privacy-policy

Dealer Login
Login
Username / Email
Password
Forgot Your Password?
Promotions
Jands Privacy PolicyUpdated March 2014Jands Pty Ltd (ABN 45 001 187 837) (Jands) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information that you provide to us. We intend to use such information for purposes of supporting our relationship with users of our manufactured and imported products. Information is collected from you for the primary purpose for which it is collected and for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose of collection. To ensure accuracy and security, Jands reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how Jands collects and uses personal information.1. Types of personal information collectedPersonal information includes information about an individual who is identified or reasonably identifiable. The personal information we collect can include: your name, company name, address, email address, telephone numbers and any other information you provide on any given website form or promotion.Any personal information gathered via this website may be retained by Jands for the purpose of processing your registration or enquiry, using your warranty details to notify you of any news related to the purchase product, keeping you informed of upcoming events and news, to create user profiles, to assist Jands in improving our service to you, or to simply contact you either electronically or otherwise.2. How personal information is collected and heldThe majority of this information is collected through forms you fill in, such as the "General Enquiry” form or promotions/competitions that we run from time to time. In all cases of direct collection Jands will state what the information will be used for. If any personal information is to be available for public access this will be explicitly stated at the time of information collection (for example online competitions).We hold personal information electronically and in hard copy form, both at our own premises and with the assistance of our service providers. We implement a range of measures to protect the security of that personal information. We also take measures in respect of destroying or de-identifying personal information that is no longer needed for any lawful purpose.3. Digital marketing and opting outBy providing your address, email address and phone numbers to Jands, you consent to Jands contacting you for the purposes set out above. We may send this information in a variety of ways, including by mail, email, social media, SMS, and telephone. You can opt out of being contacted by: contacting the Jands Marketing Department by email at marketing@jands.com.au, by phone on 02 9582 0909.advising us if you receive a marketing call that you no longer wish to receive these calls. using the unsubscribe facility that we include in our commercial electronic messages (such as emails and SMS) to opt out of receiving those messages. If you provide us with an email address or phone number, you consent to electronic communication such as notices or reminders being sent to you via that address or number. You may prefer to provide to us with your personal email address or phone number rather than, for example, an email address accessible by your work colleagues.4. Sharing of personal information Jands’ customer records are kept confidential and are used exclusively by Jands and Manufacturers of brands/products imported by Jands (including ASM, Aurora Multimedia, BSS, Cablenet, Chroma-Q, Clear-Com, Crown, dbx Professional, DIS, ETC, Furman, Gala Systems, Gator Cases, IDX, JBL Professional, Lexicon Pro, Movecat, Optocore, Pathway Connectivity, PR Lighting, Shure, Soundcraft, Spotlight, Studer, Vari*Lite and Waagner-Biro).We may also share the personal information of Jands customers with third parties where appropriate for the purposes set out above, including: Jands’ contracted service providers or partners, including: delivery and shipping providers, overseas and local agents, information technology service providers, venues and event organisers, and electronic mail houses.Regulatory, investigative or government bodies to comply with laws.We may ask one of these third parties to contact you directly for a specific purpose, and provide us with information collected from you in the course of providing the relevant products or services. We may disclose personal information to third parties that may be located in Australia and other countries such as the United States of America, Hong Kong, and the United Kingdom. We take steps to ensure that all our service providers agree to protect the privacy and security of your personal information, and use it only for the purpose for which it is disclosed.5. Data accuracy and securityThe accuracy and security of personal information is important to Jands. Jands acknowledges and respects the privacy of individuals and ensures that all information received of a personal nature will be dealt with in accordance with the Privacy Act. To that end, we put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial policies and procedures to reasonably secure your personal information.We hold personal information in a number of ways, including in printed documents, electronic databases and email contact lists. Printed documents may be held at Jands’ head office, or archived in boxes and stored in secure offsite facilities. We take reasonable steps to: ensure that the personal information that we collect, use and disclose is accurate, up to date and complete and (in the case of use and disclosure) relevant;protect the personal information that we hold from misuse, interference and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure; and destroy or permanently de-identify personal information that is no longer needed for purposes permitted by the Australian Privacy Principles. You can help us keep your information up to date, by letting us know about changes to your details. The steps we take to secure personal information include website protection measures, security restrictions on access to Jands’ computer systems, controlled access to Jands’ corporate premises, policies on document storage and security, personnel security and training and workplace policies. While we endeavour to protect the personal information of users of our website, we cannot guarantee the security of information you disclose online: you disclose that information at your own risk. If you are concerned about sending your information over the internet, you can contact Jands as set out in section 8. You can also help protect your personal information by keeping your account details confidential. If you become aware of any security breach, please let us know as soon as possible.6. Credit Card SecurityWhen purchasing from Jands, card details are transmitted through a secure server using eWay. The card data is not held by Jands Pty Limited after processing.7. CookiesThis website may use "cookies", a small data file that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to keep records of the visits to such site. Cookies do not contain information by which Jands can identify you. They identify your computer to our servers. A cookie contains information such as your username and password that helps us recognise the pages that you are allowed access to, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is the information that you provide. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. You may configure your browser so that you are notified before a cookie is downloaded or so that your browser does not accept cookies. To disable your cookies, please refer to the help menu within your Internet browser.8. Third party sitesThis website provides links to other third party websites. Links to third party sites that are not operated or controlled by Jands are provided for your convenience. Even if the third party is affiliated with Jands through a business partnership or otherwise, Jands is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of those sites, which are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Third party websites should have their own privacy and security policies, which we encourage you to read before supplying any personal information to them.9. Complaint or questionsIf you would like further information about how we manage your personal information, or would like to verify or update personal information that we may have collected about you, or if you wish to lodge a complaint in relation to an alleged breach of the Privacy Act, please direct your query to marketing@jands.com.au or 02 9582 0909.
Our Store
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Postage and Handling
Need Help?
© Copyright 2018 Jands Pty Ltd Powered by Customer Self Service from Commerce Vision
Your prices are displayed in AUD$
